All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I will be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Hordy Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It's not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict and find themselves in the midst of an all-out war.
After a change of plans, Hordy threatens to crush the entire island under the weight of a massive ship.
My acts will end this once and for all!
We were too late! It's falling!
Luffy!
It's right on target, too.
They're all going to die! Is there nothing we can do?!
Luffy loses the fight? Hordy's long-awaited revenge!
We've saja been deeply Arnold, and we've all the children and we've all the guts in this place.
But hasn't certide the 뜻 at all, a scene has been памy to each other, and I will look to you for a ritual, and we've all been for a Раз Ours!
ennesbrake Карli's faithfulician, and we've all been there.
This scene has a Untie- profile scene called Gun Selfini.
If you shoot the Powerade Arcani, you have a portrait of a piece of wounds.
You have to really seas know potato, and then, and you are always the maybeację of how Ángel by your cover and país.
But now you've just pointed out this place to answer as a tree!
So he finally gave up the ghost.
Now his ability will lose its effect, which means the Noah's about to come plummeting
down!
This is the end, Starhats!
For you and for all those who stood in the way of my vengeance!
What are we going to do now?
I don't know.
Surely there must be some way to stop the ship.
Perhaps.
But even if you could stop it, you would still have to go through me first.
And if memory serves, that didn't work out so well last time.
We'll stop you!
If the Noah falls, it spells the end for our kingdom.
And the hundreds of years that were spent protecting that legendary vessel will have been all for naught!
Listen well, my sons.
The ship of promise, Noah, is much more than some ancient relic.
Centuries ago, a promise was made to a great man.
And for our people to keep that promise, the Noah is not to be moved from the sea floor until the time is right.
Even today, there is still much we do not know about this ship, including the means by which it was constructed.
And yet, until its purpose is served, it must be protected.
It will, Father.
I swear.
You needn't worry.
We will find out why it was moved, and set this matter right.
It's not enough to save my people.
I must save the Noah as well!
Poor Starhat.
You're fresh out of hope.
Might as well just sit back and watch the show.
Because you and I both know you don't have a chance in hell of stopping me.
What's the matter?
If you're still planning to save those friends of yours from a watery grave, you'd better stop gawking and get to it.
Or did you really give up hope after all?
Whatever happened to that unfounded bravado of yours?
What a joke!
I'm not done!
I'm gonna tear that thing to pieces before it hits land!
No, you mustn't do that!
Even if you do have enough strength to destroy it, the Noah has a long history and its destined purpose is still unfulfilled!
There's no time!
You got a better way to save the island, huh?
My friends will die!
What's more important, that boat or your people?
It's possible that Deccan is simply unconscious.
If we wake him up, we may have just enough time to redirect the Noah before it's too late.
Then what if he's dead?
Then how are we gonna stop it?
We gotta destroy the ship!
Why can't you just stop and think things through?
Not getting along, are we?
Well, while you're arguing, just know your time is running out.
Please don't fall, Noah!
The people on Fishman Island are very dear to me!
Sir Deccan!
If you're still living, then please allow me to become the Noah's target once again!
Have mercy on the island, I beg of you!
I think I'll go ahead and kill you now!
I'm afraid you'll have to witness the destruction of the Ryugu Kingdom from beyond the grave!
Fishman Karate!
Jirozi!
And Sidron!
Are you alright, brother?
Bambushi!
Don't think for a moment I've forgotten about you!
Fishman!
Cut it!
Knock it off!
Move aside, boy!
Second gear!
Gumb gumb!
Dammit!
The armament hunky protects me against punches!
But I guess this is too much!
Gotta watch out for those teeth!
Being underwater's not helping me either!
Only one way to beat this guy!
Now let's go!
So the little coward wants to fight me on the Noah!
Right!
Cause there's air on the deck!
Smart move!
But I'm still smarter!
If I can get in there!
I can beat him with one hit!
I knew it!
He's cutting through!
Oh no!
So sorry to burst your bubble straw hat!
That's no good!
How am I gonna beat him if I can't even breathe?
You humans aren't nearly so tough when you're out of your element!
You're even weaker than a fish out of water one might say!
If you're no match for me!
How can you hope to stop the Noah?
It's over!
Just die!
No!
Come come!
Nature!
Come on!
Do you think I'd be stupid enough to be hit by the same attack twice?
So which will be first?
All your companions being crushed under the weight of the Noah?
Or you embracing death at my hands?
I wonder!
Crap!
If he breaks my bubble again I am dead!
This is getting old, straw hat!
A hat!
Uh...
Muffy!
Sister!
Yes, what is it Fukuboshi?
Please listen carefully.
Straw Hat...
Is in your hands now.
What should I...
As for me...
I must stop Hordi somehow.
Sister.
You may not understand, but trust me.
Do not stray from the Noah!
No matter what happens.
Alright?
Uh...
Yes.
This is just too easy.
There's no way I can miss you now.
Uh...
Dammit!
Time to say goodbye!
What happened?
I'm here.
Forgive me if that was rough.
Weepy Hoshi!
Hey!
Fukuboshi asked me to help you in his stead.
He's gonna fight?
This is sick.
What did those people ever do to you?
What kind of heartless person values life so little?
Tell me!
Better heartless than weak, right?
You three are supposed to be the strongest in the Ryugu kingdom.
Just look at you!
Though what can you expect from the sons of that spineless Otuhime?
Without an ounce of pride for her race, it's no wonder she died like a dog trying to get along with humans.
That's her only legacy!
And three useless sons who can't save their own kingdom.
What are they doing?
He's coming back this way!
I'm not too proud to admit.
Even though your power was falsely acquired, I wasn't strong enough to vanquish you.
But still, I have hope!
Merman combat!
Ultramarine technique!
You still don't get it, do you?
It's a lost cause!
You can't even put a scratch on me!
What I don't understand, Horty, is how you can seek to destroy so many of your fellow men and still feel nothing!
What is it you want that's worth killing for?
What do you stand to gain if Fishman Island ceases to be?
Stop this!
Ultramarine!
Farewell!
Noonan!
I can't help!
Oh noha!
But idea there is no reward.
I will start out.
Just leave, except him will use his开始 to tell you.
Too bad, you pitiful prince.
Listen, where it came from, my power's quite real.
Okay, all that's left now is to get rid of you two.
Dammit!
Mark my words, your ill-gotten strength will never best me.
A little late to be saying that.
Forty, what's happened to you?
At first, you wanted our people to rise up against humans.
This makes sense, even if it's misguided.
But now you would have the entire population of Fishman Island be put to death instead.
There are people living in the Fishman District who were once your allies.
What you're doing doesn't benefit anyone, not even you.
Why can't you see that, Hordy?
Is there something I don't know?
Or is your hatred so deep that you've abandoned your sense of reason entirely?
Tell me the cause of this madness.
Did humans attack you?
Did they torment you in some untold manner?
Did they kill your friends?
Did they hurt your family?
Did they take something you hold dear?
Answer me, dammit!
What did humans do to you that was so unforgivable?
Why?
What in this world could inspire such cruelty?
Brother, please don't die!
Seriously? Hey! Your brother needs us! Let's go!
Come on, Weepiho-shi! Snap out of it!
Where are we going? Hold on!
Sister, you may not understand, but trust me, do not stray from the Noah, no matter what happens, all right?
Weepiho-shi!
Strawhead Luffy, this is the air tank. We've met before, remember?
Oh, yeah, hey guys!
We've been listening to what's happening out there. And we can see the Noah hurtling toward the island. We've begun making the preparations as we've discussed.
So that's what Brother Hoshi meant before.
I've got business there too. What is this?
Well, aren't you gonna go?
Not yet. We must be cautious.
But if we don't follow him, he'll get away!
Hori's obviously up to something here. And more importantly, we have to be ready to face him underwater again. Stay alert.
So what do we do?
I have an idea.
Hey! Where are we off to? Brother Hoshi?
Prince Fukuboshi? What brings you here?
It's quite possible that we're going to need a large amount of air very soon. Please make arrangements for us.
Sir!
I can handle this. There's supposed to be some air on the deck, right? If I can breathe, there's no problem.
Deccan needs the bubble. That much is true. However, Horty may still destroy it if worse comes to worse.
Take this baby transponder snail. This will be our last resort in the event that things go poorly. We must be prepared for anything.
Oh, Luffy. I don't know what to do!
My brother told me that I should protect you and stay close to the Noah at any cost. But I don't understand what good that will do us now!
Hang on. I think I know.
Hey guys! What do we need to do to get a little air from you?
We can shoot out all the air in the air tank.
What is that thing for, anyway?
It's an air conditioning facility that provides air for Fishman Island. If we create a big bubble and shoot it, maybe it'll surround the Noah.
However, the bubble would neutralize ascending forces, so it's not going to make the Noah stop or reverse course.
On top of that, we'd have to use all the air we've got to make the bubble big enough to hold the ship. And it would crash long before we could resupply.
What I mean is we've got only one chance. If we don't manage to send out the bubble at the exact moment the Noah moves closest to the air tank, then we're done. It's over.
All riding on one shot, huh? Wow. Better not miss.
Right. I'm afraid that's all we can do. After we deploy the bubble, the rest is up to you. I should reiterate, this is-
Don't make it more complicated. Just go for it, okay? If I can breathe, I'll make this work.
All right, roger that. We'll do our best not to miss the ship. And Luffy, everyone here is counting on you.
They're swimming alongside it. You're just a lowly human and a cowardly mermaid. What can you two possibly hope to accomplish now?
Shark Tracer!
Out of my way.
Gormon Harsing!
No way, he got even bigger?
Ready to give up.
You should be human.
Just the sight of you vile worms makes me sick to my stomach.
Even if it shortens my life and even if I have to sacrifice everything in this world.
I swear to you, I will have my revenge against the human race.
Hordy!
You've only got one shot, so you better not miss it.
If this doesn't work, the whole island's done for.
Can you hear me, Straw Hat?
Oh dear, that's my brother's voice!
Hey buddy, are you okay?
I'm barely alive, but please listen.
He spoke earlier and...
It's clear now. Hordy is...
...
The Straw Hats continue their battle with the new Fishman Pirates, having faith that Luffy will carry out his mission.
Neptune's army aids them in the struggle,
finally accepting the crew as allies.
As the fight continues, Fukuboshi's transponder snail
reveals the sober truth behind Horty's motivations
to all of Fishman Island.
On the next One Piece, a shocking fact,
the true identity of Horty,
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!